CURTIS CALI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Henderson, Nevada, United States 408 315 6627 curtiscali@pm.me https://ccali.dev

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Results-oriented software developer with five years experience and a Software Engineering BS. Proven problem-solving and collaboration skills. Able to adapt to new tech stacks and technologies as demanded by the needs of the project. Worked on several full-stack web and mobile development projects. Seeking remote development work with an exciting growth company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOLUTIONS DEVELOPER

Chainbridge Technologies | Vienna, VA | Jun 2017 - Present At Chainbridge Technologies, I developed logistics and data collection software for various federal agencies including the DOE and FEMA. In performing my duties, I worked with both local and remote employees located all over the country, maintaining consistent communication with all relevant team members. I also worked diligently in order to ensure business requirements were clarified and met. I designed & developed

- Wrote 75% of the ARMS mobile app used by DOE and ensured consistent quality in releases with minimal delay.
- Overhauled the UX of the ARMS Website cutting navigation time in half.

new features and fixed bugs in various software systems as needed.

- Enhanced FEMA's mobile data collection capabilities by ensuring 5 successful releases for the RadResponder Mobile App
- Wrote Android & iOS apps to help the members DOD learn how to use and develop mobile apps for CBRNResponder's external REST

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

Cisco Systems | San Jose, CA | May 2016 - Aug 2016

I implemented a REST API for Google Maps to improve loading performance by 95%, panning performance by 15%, and zooming performance by 9%

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Datto Inc | Norwalk, CT | Jun 2015 - Aug 2015

Assisted with development of prototype product Datto Network Appliance (DNA). Implemented network failover prioritization, refined graphs with D3, enhanced test scripts.

LABS SOFTWARE INTERN

EnerNOC | Boston, MA | Jan 2015 - May 2015

Performed development for various projects in EnerNOC Labs including software to aid the marketing department in selling Energy Intelligence Software and a REST API for the Automated Load Control platform.

EDUCATION

B.S. SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Rochester Institute of Technology | Rochester, NY | 2012 - 2017

SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Relational Databases (SQL)
- Web Development
- Durandal/Knockout JS

- Attention to detail
- C#/.NET Framework
- Mobile Development

- **Quick Learning**
- Xamarin Forms
- Javascript/HTML

PERSONAL

I love dogs, walking, streaming amazing shows, and exploring the beautiful Nevada desert.